pkr.com 2011-05-31

# PKR | Poker support | PKR Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy governs the www.pkr.com website ("the Site").

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect your personal information on the Site, how we protect such information, our processing of and your choices concerning the use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "We", "Us" and "Our" means PKR Limited.

This Privacy Policy represents Our current data collection and usage practices. We will, from time to time, review and revise these practices. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using the Site or any of the products, offerings, features, tools or resources that we provide on the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by the Site and/or through your registration. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g. message board or chat room), or for the privacy practices of websites that you may access via the Site but which are operated or owned by third parties

### Collection of Personal Information

Personal information is information about you and that identifies you or can be used to identify you (in conjunction with any other information We have about you) e.g. your name, e-mail address, address or telephone number ("Personal Information"). You may browse certain pages of the Site without registering with Us first. If you do so, We will not process your Personal Information but may use your Non-Personal information as set out below.

In order to access Our Games (as defined in Our terms and conditions) and certain other services available on the Site from time to time you will need to register with Us. In order to process your registration, and provide such services to you, We will need from time to time to obtain Personal Information from you which may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and expiry date or bank account details.

Any Personal Information you provide may be used by Us or third parties appointed by Us to process such information in order to allow you to play the Games and otherwise make use of the services and functionality of the Site and for matters reasonably connected with such use. However, unless you give Us permission to do so, we will not share, license, trade or rent your Personal Information other than as specified in this Privacy Policy.

### Collection of Non-personal Information

In addition to Personal Information, we may collect and/or track information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, e.g. demographic information (such as age, profession or gender), domain names, computer type, browser type and other anonymous statistical data ("Non-personal Information"). We use Non-personal Information to help Us understand who uses the Site and to improve and market the Site.

We may collect your Non-personal Information even where you choose not to register on the Site. We do this by use of tracking tools which consist of various Internet technologies such as "cookies", "action tags", "web bugs", ".gif tags" and "JavaScript" (together, "Tracking Tools"). Tracking Tools are files or tools that are placed on your computer in order to identify your Web browser and your activity on the Site. Tracking Tools enable us to develop a profile about your preferences on the Site and to show you information that you have indicated that you are interested in. In this way, we can customise and improve your experience on the Site.

You may disable cookies, if any, by using the appropriate feature of your Web browser software. If cookies are disabled, however, you may not be able to benefit from all features of the Site.

### Use of information collected

We may use your Personal Information for Our own business purposes in connection with the running of the Site, including for feedback purposes, for the provision of services to you, for marketing and promotion, for statistical analysis of users' behaviour, for product development and for content improvement. We may also pass your Personal Information to companies affiliated with Us and any authorised agents and sub-contractors for the purposes of carrying out the foregoing activities, and to customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes. In the event that Our business is sold to or integrated with another business your Personal Information may be disclosed to Our advisers and any prospective purchasers' advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business. We will not otherwise disclose any of your Personal Information to third parties, except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws, rules or regulations. Certain of the services provided or accessible through our Site, in particular, the gaming and payment processing services, may be regulated by one or more government authorities. As such, your Personal Information may be recorded and passed to the relevant authorities. In addition We may pass your Personal Information to any relevant police or other investigatory agency where We in our reasonable discretion consider that We are required to comply with a request from such agency. We may conduct credit searches on you, verify your bank details and share information with other providers of similar services to those available on the Site in the interests of ensuring the security and integrity of the Games.

We reserve the right to use your Personal Information to contact you in relation to your account status, changes to this Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relating to your use of the Site.

We may also use Non-personal Information for the purposes of monitoring Site usage in order to help Us develop Our Site and the services and for these purposes We may provide Non-personal Information to third parties.

To ensure that your credit, debit or charge card is not being used without your consent, we will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you during the order process against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

### Your choices regarding your Personal Information

From time to time We may provide information that We have gathered about you to Our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that We can monitor and improve the services We provide. We may contact you by post, e-mail or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on Our services. If you do not want to be contacted for your views, please let Our customer services department know.

We and Our affiliated companies may also wish to provide you with information about special features or offers on the Site or any other service or products which We think may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive this information, please let Our customer services department know.

Upon request We will provide you with a summary of all Personal Information held about you which we are required by law to disclose. Any such access request may be subject to a fee to meet Our costs in providing you with details of information We hold about you.

### How we protect your information

We have put in place various security procedures to try to ensure that the information you have provided to Us remains confidential and is protected from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

We also have technical measures in place so that whenever you undertake any financial transactions through Our Site (including engaging in gaming), this will take place over a secure link which will encrypt the information whilst it is travelling over the Internet. Furthermore, any communications with banking or credit providers through Our Site will similarly be encrypted. Firewalls are used to block unauthorised traffic to the servers and the actual servers are located in a secure location which can only be accessed by authorised personnel.

Please note that while We have tried to create a secure and reliable site for users, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from Us via the Site cannot be guaranteed.

### Where we store your Personal Information

The Personal Information that We collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside Alderney and the European Economic Area ("the EEA") . It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for Us or for one of Our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, amongst other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your Personal Information to Us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

### Updating your Personal Information

If any of the information that you have provided to Us changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let Us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to Our customer services department.

### How to contact PKR

We welcome your views about the Site and our Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact Us with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to Our customer services department.

### Jurisdiction

This Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Alderney whose courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction in any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, save that we have the right, at Our sole discretion, to commence and pursue proceedings in alternative jurisdictions.
